{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848428723","data":{"timestamp":" 946848428722"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848436039","data":{"timestamp":" 946848436039"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848437636","data":{"timestamp":" 946848437636"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848442770","data":{"timestamp":" 946848442770"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848444340","data":{"timestamp":" 946848444339"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848447817","data":{"timestamp":" 946848447817"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848449374","data":{"timestamp":" 946848449374"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848453130","data":{"timestamp":" 946848453130"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848454702","data":{"timestamp":" 946848454702"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848457843","data":{"timestamp":" 946848457843"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848459415","data":{"timestamp":" 946848459415"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848462500","data":{"timestamp":" 946848462500"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848464072","data":{"timestamp":" 946848464072"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" PILIPILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848468031","data":{"timestamp":" 946848468031"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PILIPILI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILIPILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848469593","data":{"timestamp":" 946848469593"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848472837","data":{"timestamp":" 946848472837"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848474391","data":{"timestamp":" 946848474391"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" PAPAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848477769","data":{"timestamp":" 946848477769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAPAI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAPAI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848479327","data":{"timestamp":" 946848479326"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" PARACHICHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848483420","data":{"timestamp":" 946848483420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PARACHICHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PARACHICHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848484993","data":{"timestamp":" 946848484993"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" PINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848488429","data":{"timestamp":" 946848488429"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PINI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848489995","data":{"timestamp":" 946848489995"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848493578","data":{"timestamp":" 946848493578"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848495136","data":{"timestamp":" 946848495136"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" PAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848499252","data":{"timestamp":" 946848499252"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848501266","data":{"timestamp":" 946848501266"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848501420","data":{"timestamp":" 946848501420"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" bff83ac4-e075-482b-a090-bf5d79eed208"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848513896","data":{"timestamp":" 946848513896"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848517472","data":{"timestamp":" 946848517472"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDAMILIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDAMILIA"," userResponse":" PUNDAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848519068","data":{"timestamp":" 946848519067"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" POLISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848522044","data":{"timestamp":" 946848522044"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" START_POLISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848557399","data":{"timestamp":" 946848557399"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" POLISI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848559002","data":{"timestamp":" 946848559002"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" PERA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848562745","data":{"timestamp":" 946848562744"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PERA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PERA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848564305","data":{"timestamp":" 946848564305"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848568005","data":{"timestamp":" 946848568004"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PACHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848569645","data":{"timestamp":" 946848569644"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848574785","data":{"timestamp":" 946848574784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PANYA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848576464","data":{"timestamp":" 946848576464"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848576484","data":{"timestamp":" 946848576483"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-P.rand.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848602352","data":{"timestamp":" 946848602352"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848602459","data":{"timestamp":" 946848602459"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.mc.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848609925","data":{"timestamp":" 946848609924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.show.57","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848616384","data":{"timestamp":" 946848616383"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 83cfbb35-b9b0-4046-aae0-2199dd252d87"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-P.rand.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" PUNDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848628556","data":{"timestamp":" 946848628555"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848629155","data":{"timestamp":" 946848629154"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848629885","data":{"timestamp":" 946848629884"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848630064","data":{"timestamp":" 946848630064"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848630851","data":{"timestamp":" 946848630850"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATATIZO"," userResponse":" MATATIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848631884","data":{"timestamp":" 946848631883"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji changu kilikuwa na matatizo mengi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848634687","data":{"timestamp":" 946848634687"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPANGA"," userResponse":" TULIPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848635380","data":{"timestamp":" 946848635379"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOLENI"," userResponse":" FOLENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848636648","data":{"timestamp":" 946848636648"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848638324","data":{"timestamp":" 946848638323"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848639067","data":{"timestamp":" 946848639067"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOTA"," userResponse":" KUCHOTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848639925","data":{"timestamp":" 946848639924"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848640800","data":{"timestamp":" 946848640799"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848641535","data":{"timestamp":" 946848641535"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848642211","data":{"timestamp":" 946848642210"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulipanga foleni ndefu tukisubiri kuchota maji kutoka mfereji mmoja."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848645793","data":{"timestamp":" 946848645793"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISUBIRI"," userResponse":" TULISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848646336","data":{"timestamp":" 946848646336"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848646484","data":{"timestamp":" 946848646484"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848646890","data":{"timestamp":" 946848646889"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848647726","data":{"timestamp":" 946848647726"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848648657","data":{"timestamp":" 946848648656"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPOKEA"," userResponse":" KUPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848649354","data":{"timestamp":" 946848649354"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848649512","data":{"timestamp":" 946848649512"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848650274","data":{"timestamp":" 946848650274"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulisubiri chini ya mti mkubwa kupokea msaada wa chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848653431","data":{"timestamp":" 946848653431"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFUNGA"," userResponse":" TULIFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848653916","data":{"timestamp":" 946848653916"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848654440","data":{"timestamp":" 946848654440"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848655231","data":{"timestamp":" 946848655230"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPEMA"," userResponse":" MAPEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848655885","data":{"timestamp":" 946848655884"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848656533","data":{"timestamp":" 946848656533"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJILI"," userResponse":" AJILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848656620","data":{"timestamp":" 946848656619"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848657217","data":{"timestamp":" 946848657217"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulifunga nyumba zetu mapema kwa ajili ya wizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIZI"," userResponse":" WIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848660406","data":{"timestamp":" 946848660406"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADHI"," userResponse":" BAADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848660539","data":{"timestamp":" 946848660539"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848661484","data":{"timestamp":" 946848661483"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848662562","data":{"timestamp":" 946848662561"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIACHA"," userResponse":" WALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848663231","data":{"timestamp":" 946848663231"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848663683","data":{"timestamp":" 946848663683"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848664319","data":{"timestamp":" 946848664318"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848664860","data":{"timestamp":" 946848664860"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848665354","data":{"timestamp":" 946848665353"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848666737","data":{"timestamp":" 946848666737"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848667397","data":{"timestamp":" 946848667396"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIPA"," userResponse":" KULIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848667994","data":{"timestamp":" 946848667994"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadhi ya watoto waliacha shule kwa sababu wazazi wao hawakuweza kulipa karo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848670949","data":{"timestamp":" 946848670948"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASICHANA"," userResponse":" WASICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848671332","data":{"timestamp":" 946848671331"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848672336","data":{"timestamp":" 946848672336"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848672853","data":{"timestamp":" 946848672853"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848673825","data":{"timestamp":" 946848673825"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848674479","data":{"timestamp":" 946848674478"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848675102","data":{"timestamp":" 946848675102"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wasichana wadogo walifanya kazi kijijini kama yaya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAYA"," userResponse":" YAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848678104","data":{"timestamp":" 946848678103"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVULANA"," userResponse":" WAVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848678859","data":{"timestamp":" 946848678859"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WADOGO"," userResponse":" WADOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848679682","data":{"timestamp":" 946848679681"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRANDA"," userResponse":" WALIRANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848680187","data":{"timestamp":" 946848680186"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANDA"," userResponse":" RANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848681133","data":{"timestamp":" 946848681133"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJINI"," userResponse":" KIJIJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848681778","data":{"timestamp":" 946848681777"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848682395","data":{"timestamp":" 946848682395"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENGINE"," userResponse":" WENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848683344","data":{"timestamp":" 946848683343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIFANYIA"," userResponse":" WAKIFANYIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848683797","data":{"timestamp":" 946848683797"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848684269","data":{"timestamp":" 946848684268"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848685251","data":{"timestamp":" 946848685250"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wavulana wadogo waliranda randa kijijini huku wengine wakifanyia watu kazi mashambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHAMBANI"," userResponse":" MASHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848688338","data":{"timestamp":" 946848688337"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848689646","data":{"timestamp":" 946848689646"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOVUMA"," userResponse":" ULIPOVUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848691391","data":{"timestamp":" 946848691390"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," userResponse":" ULIPEPERUSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848692197","data":{"timestamp":" 946848692197"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARATASI"," userResponse":" KARATASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848693045","data":{"timestamp":" 946848693045"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAFU"," userResponse":" CHAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848693517","data":{"timestamp":" 946848693517"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848694754","data":{"timestamp":" 946848694754"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUZIANGIKA"," userResponse":" KUZIANGIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848695790","data":{"timestamp":" 946848695790"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITINI"," userResponse":" MITINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848696256","data":{"timestamp":" 946848696256"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848696879","data":{"timestamp":" 946848696878"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upepo ulipovuma ulipeperusha karatasi chafu na kuziangika mitini na uani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UANI"," userResponse":" UANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848700286","data":{"timestamp":" 946848700285"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIANI"," userResponse":" NJIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848700883","data":{"timestamp":" 946848700883"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848701822","data":{"timestamp":" 946848701822"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848702005","data":{"timestamp":" 946848702005"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848702751","data":{"timestamp":" 946848702751"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPANDE"," userResponse":" VIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848703002","data":{"timestamp":" 946848703001"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848703640","data":{"timestamp":" 946848703639"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUPA"," userResponse":" CHUPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848705036","data":{"timestamp":" 946848705035"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," userResponse":" VILIVYOTUPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848705387","data":{"timestamp":" 946848705386"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848705869","data":{"timestamp":" 946848705868"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Njiani watu walikatwa na vipande vya chupa vilivyotupwa ovyo ovyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVYO"," userResponse":" OVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848709455","data":{"timestamp":" 946848709455"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALAFU"," userResponse":" HALAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848709907","data":{"timestamp":" 946848709907"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848710563","data":{"timestamp":" 946848710562"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848711858","data":{"timestamp":" 946848711858"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFEREJI"," userResponse":" MFEREJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848712056","data":{"timestamp":" 946848712055"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848712656","data":{"timestamp":" 946848712655"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848713890","data":{"timestamp":" 946848713889"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKAUKA"," userResponse":" ULIKAUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848714586","data":{"timestamp":" 946848714586"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848715448","data":{"timestamp":" 946848715447"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITUNGI"," userResponse":" MITUNGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848715889","data":{"timestamp":" 946848715889"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848717037","data":{"timestamp":" 946848717037"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAWA"," userResponse":" IKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848717769","data":{"timestamp":" 946848717769"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Halafu siku moja mfereji wa maji ulikauka na mitungi yetu ikawa tupu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUPU"," userResponse":" TUPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848720885","data":{"timestamp":" 946848720885"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848722148","data":{"timestamp":" 946848722148"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITEMBEA"," userResponse":" ALITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848722925","data":{"timestamp":" 946848722925"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848723561","data":{"timestamp":" 946848723560"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848724352","data":{"timestamp":" 946848724351"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848724921","data":{"timestamp":" 946848724921"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848726241","data":{"timestamp":" 946848726241"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWAALIKA"," userResponse":" AKIWAALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848726768","data":{"timestamp":" 946848726768"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848728013","data":{"timestamp":" 946848728012"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUDHURIA"," userResponse":" KUHUDHURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848728855","data":{"timestamp":" 946848728855"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUTANO"," userResponse":" MKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848729076","data":{"timestamp":" 946848729076"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848729903","data":{"timestamp":" 946848729903"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alitembea kutoka nyumba hadi nyumba akiwaalika watu kuhudhuria mkutano wa kujiji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIJI"," userResponse":" KUJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848732672","data":{"timestamp":" 946848732672"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848733933","data":{"timestamp":" 946848733932"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," userResponse":" WALIKUSANYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848734510","data":{"timestamp":" 946848734510"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848734593","data":{"timestamp":" 946848734593"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848735034","data":{"timestamp":" 946848735033"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848735599","data":{"timestamp":" 946848735599"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848736000","data":{"timestamp":" 946848735999"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULE"," userResponse":" ULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848736943","data":{"timestamp":" 946848736942"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAKO"," userResponse":" AMBAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848737815","data":{"timestamp":" 946848737814"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOKEA"," userResponse":" TULIPOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848738392","data":{"timestamp":" 946848738391"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848738651","data":{"timestamp":" 946848738650"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848739413","data":{"timestamp":" 946848739413"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walikusanyika chini ya mti ule ule ambako tulipokea chakula cha msaada."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAADA"," userResponse":" MSAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848742442","data":{"timestamp":" 946848742441"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABANGU"," userResponse":" BABANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848743339","data":{"timestamp":" 946848743339"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848744465","data":{"timestamp":" 946848744464"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848744955","data":{"timestamp":" 946848744953"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848745832","data":{"timestamp":" 946848745831"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKUNDI"," userResponse":" KIKUNDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848746238","data":{"timestamp":" 946848746237"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848746984","data":{"timestamp":" 946848746984"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848748299","data":{"timestamp":" 946848748299"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848749520","data":{"timestamp":" 946848749520"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUREKEBISHE"," userResponse":" TUREKEBISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848750079","data":{"timestamp":" 946848750079"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848750729","data":{"timestamp":" 946848750728"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Babangu alisimama katikati ya kikundi na kusema Lazima turekebishe kijiji chetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848754234","data":{"timestamp":" 946848754234"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUMA"," userResponse":" JUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848755456","data":{"timestamp":" 946848755455"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848756327","data":{"timestamp":" 946848756326"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEPANDA"," userResponse":" AMEPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848756949","data":{"timestamp":" 946848756949"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848757877","data":{"timestamp":" 946848757876"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848758171","data":{"timestamp":" 946848758171"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848758825","data":{"timestamp":" 946848758825"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848759860","data":{"timestamp":" 946848759859"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848760958","data":{"timestamp":" 946848760957"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFISHA"," userResponse":" KUSAFISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848761603","data":{"timestamp":" 946848761603"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UWANJA"," userResponse":" UWANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848761767","data":{"timestamp":" 946848761766"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848762186","data":{"timestamp":" 946848762185"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848762903","data":{"timestamp":" 946848762903"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Juma aliyekuwa amepanda mti alisema kwa sauti Naweza kusafisha uwanja wa nyumba yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848766032","data":{"timestamp":" 946848766032"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848766591","data":{"timestamp":" 946848766590"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848766768","data":{"timestamp":" 946848766767"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848767549","data":{"timestamp":" 946848767549"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKAMO"," userResponse":" MAKAMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848768366","data":{"timestamp":" 946848768366"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848769342","data":{"timestamp":" 946848769342"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848770306","data":{"timestamp":" 946848770305"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848771301","data":{"timestamp":" 946848771301"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAWEZA"," userResponse":" TUNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848772059","data":{"timestamp":" 946848772058"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUNGANA"," userResponse":" KUUNGANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848772256","data":{"timestamp":" 946848772256"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848772863","data":{"timestamp":" 946848772862"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPANDA"," userResponse":" KUPANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848773658","data":{"timestamp":" 946848773657"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke mmoja wa makamo alisema Sisi wanawake tunaweza kuungana na kupanda chakula."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848776742","data":{"timestamp":" 946848776741"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848777585","data":{"timestamp":" 946848777585"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848778556","data":{"timestamp":" 946848778556"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIMAMA"," userResponse":" ALISIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848778763","data":{"timestamp":" 946848778762"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848779422","data":{"timestamp":" 946848779422"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSEMA"," userResponse":" KUSEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848780601","data":{"timestamp":" 946848780601"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848781504","data":{"timestamp":" 946848781504"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATACHIMBA"," userResponse":" WATACHIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848782077","data":{"timestamp":" 946848782077"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISIMA"," userResponse":" KISIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848782344","data":{"timestamp":" 946848782343"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848783042","data":{"timestamp":" 946848783041"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamme mwingine alisimama na kusema Wanaume watachimba kisima cha maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848786167","data":{"timestamp":" 946848786167"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848787045","data":{"timestamp":" 946848787045"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULISEMA"," userResponse":" TULISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848787285","data":{"timestamp":" 946848787285"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848787956","data":{"timestamp":" 946848787956"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848788454","data":{"timestamp":" 946848788453"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848789831","data":{"timestamp":" 946848789830"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848790966","data":{"timestamp":" 946848790965"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUBADILISHE"," userResponse":" TUBADILISHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848791702","data":{"timestamp":" 946848791702"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848792406","data":{"timestamp":" 946848792406"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tulisema kwa sauti moja Lazima tubadilishe maisha yetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848794798","data":{"timestamp":" 946848794798"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848795271","data":{"timestamp":" 946848795271"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848795928","data":{"timestamp":" 946848795926"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848797007","data":{"timestamp":" 946848797006"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIFANYA"," userResponse":" TULIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848797494","data":{"timestamp":" 946848797494"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848798477","data":{"timestamp":" 946848798477"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848799874","data":{"timestamp":" 946848799873"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKATATUA"," userResponse":" TUKATATUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848800369","data":{"timestamp":" 946848800369"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIDA"," userResponse":" SHIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848800740","data":{"timestamp":" 946848800739"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848803615","data":{"timestamp":" 946848803614"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848803689","data":{"timestamp":" 946848803689"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZETU"," userResponse":" ZETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:P..P.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.58","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848810373","data":{"timestamp":" 946848810373"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" f57a5f13-467e-4613-bc94-24fd904a1133"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_35"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Tangu siku hiyo tulifanya kazi pamoja tukatatua shida zetu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848828383","data":{"timestamp":" 946848828383"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 428d3b7b-f2ef-457f-ac90-4f935d6152f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848845408","data":{"timestamp":" 946848845408"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 428d3b7b-f2ef-457f-ac90-4f935d6152f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848851651","data":{"timestamp":" 946848851651"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 428d3b7b-f2ef-457f-ac90-4f935d6152f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848857434","data":{"timestamp":" 946848857434"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 428d3b7b-f2ef-457f-ac90-4f935d6152f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848865628","data":{"timestamp":" 946848865628"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 428d3b7b-f2ef-457f-ac90-4f935d6152f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848932505","data":{"timestamp":" 946848932505"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 428d3b7b-f2ef-457f-ac90-4f935d6152f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848936158","data":{"timestamp":" 946848936157"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 428d3b7b-f2ef-457f-ac90-4f935d6152f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:P..P.all.10.rand.say.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946848948192","data":{"timestamp":" 946848948191"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 428d3b7b-f2ef-457f-ac90-4f935d6152f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849094302","data":{"timestamp":" 946849094301"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 428d3b7b-f2ef-457f-ac90-4f935d6152f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849094441","data":{"timestamp":" 946849094441"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 3e437aa2-8c0e-4dbd-9ff8-87819401bd28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849101685","data":{"timestamp":" 946849101684"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 3e437aa2-8c0e-4dbd-9ff8-87819401bd28"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849113998","data":{"timestamp":" 946849113998"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849118720","data":{"timestamp":" 946849118719"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_2-3-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849124381","data":{"timestamp":" 946849124380"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-3-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849130784","data":{"timestamp":" 946849130784"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-2"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849141670","data":{"timestamp":" 946849141670"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-3-1"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849147605","data":{"timestamp":" 946849147605"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_4-1-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849152696","data":{"timestamp":" 946849152696"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2-1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849157419","data":{"timestamp":" 946849157419"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849162943","data":{"timestamp":" 946849162943"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849168080","data":{"timestamp":" 946849168080"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849174014","data":{"timestamp":" 946849174014"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849186715","data":{"timestamp":" 946849186715"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" fa85afe2-c8ff-445e-9ddf-7f58e15efcd4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_1..4.by.1.asc.s2q.AV.rise.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-2"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849319004","data":{"timestamp":" 946849319004"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849329377","data":{"timestamp":" 946849329377"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849337305","data":{"timestamp":" 946849337305"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849353645","data":{"timestamp":" 946849353645"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849384087","data":{"timestamp":" 946849384087"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849397449","data":{"timestamp":" 946849397449"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849400689","data":{"timestamp":" 946849400689"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849417083","data":{"timestamp":" 946849417083"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849453155","data":{"timestamp":" 946849453155"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849464576","data":{"timestamp":" 946849464576"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num:WR-1..20.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849468638","data":{"timestamp":" 946849468637"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 29e493f0-ff61-4b71-a0ed-dfcd33dfb63c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num_WR-1..20.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849480077","data":{"timestamp":" 946849480077"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 0c7a96b3-1f81-4cba-8d4e-73f966cc3ed4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849482913","data":{"timestamp":" 946849482912"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 0c7a96b3-1f81-4cba-8d4e-73f966cc3ed4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849484490","data":{"timestamp":" 946849484490"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 0c7a96b3-1f81-4cba-8d4e-73f966cc3ed4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849488327","data":{"timestamp":" 946849488327"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 0c7a96b3-1f81-4cba-8d4e-73f966cc3ed4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849489901","data":{"timestamp":" 946849489900"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 0c7a96b3-1f81-4cba-8d4e-73f966cc3ed4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849493139","data":{"timestamp":" 946849493139"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 0c7a96b3-1f81-4cba-8d4e-73f966cc3ed4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849494704","data":{"timestamp":" 946849494704"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 0c7a96b3-1f81-4cba-8d4e-73f966cc3ed4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849497262","data":{"timestamp":" 946849497262"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 0c7a96b3-1f81-4cba-8d4e-73f966cc3ed4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946849497453","data":{"timestamp":" 946849497453"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000103_002638"," gameId":" 0c7a96b3-1f81-4cba-8d4e-73f966cc3ed4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_16"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}